CLARANCE LIBERISTE NTWARI

SOFTWARE ENGINEER | TYPESCRIPT & NODE.JS



ABOUT

RWANDA

☐ LIBERINTWARI@GMAIL.COM

in IN/CLARANCE-LIBERISTE-NTWARI-27A484184 [7]

CLARANCELIBERI

WEBPACK

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH (PROFESSIONAL LANGUAGE)

KINYARWANDA (NATIVE LANGUAGE)

SUMMARY

Programmer with over 5 years of experience who is creative, dedicated, and enthusiastic about their work. Competent with Typescript, React, Vue, and Node.js My experience as a team leader in two different Agile frameworks (Kanban and Scrum) and three years of working remotely has made me flexible and taught me the value of clear and effective communication.

EXPERIENCE

07/2022 - PRESENT

SENIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

By simplifying end-to-end fleet management and offering guidance on how to decarbonize their fleet, a one-stop digital platform operating on BP's Superfleet platform assists fleet managers who want to maximize the efficiency of their fleet. This frees up time to expand their business in a Net Zero world. - I contributed to the Notification Team (Squad), ensuring that Superfleet users may improve their platform experiences by not missing any action or insight made on the platform. - I was a part of the Audit Trail Team, whose job it was to keep a log of all the platform's users' past actions. - Involvement in Domains Team, managing high-level monorepo architecture for efficient team development and CI/CD pipelines NX | React.js | Typescript | Webpack | Node.js | Azure Devops

04/2021 - 06/2022

FULL STACK ENGINEER

HuntersOfBook is a community for avid readers who want to meet new individuals who share their interest in books. Technically I: - Created a storybook-like representation of UI elements to streamline frontend development, - Created a simple WYSIWYG editor for platform articles Used GraphQL for Integration Between Backend and Frontend Services GraphQL | Typescript | Vue.js | Node.js | Nest.js | Tailwind | Javascript

07/2020 - 03/2021

QA ENGINEER

I have used Golang to perform stress testing, during which I was required to send 10,000 requests per second, and I have conducted both Blackbox and Whitebox tests on the API level and the frontend. GoLang | Typescript | Javascript | Postman

01/2019 - 05/2020

FRONTEND ENGINEER

Kurious is an online learning platform that competes with public alternatives like Coursera and Edx but is exclusive to independent educational institutions. - Many of the front-end tools that enable colleges to provide video and textual materials to students were created by me. - I built a front-end messaging service that lets people have a group or individual conversations in real-time, whether in school or not. Vue.js | Nuxt.js.| Typescript | Docker | MongoDb| Node.js | SCSS

12/2019 - 12/2019

WEB DEVELOPMENT MENTOR

During my time in the program, I helped teach programming concepts to around three hundred and fifty under 18 children. On of the skills covered was: - HTML - CSS - $\mathsf{Javascript}$ - PHP - SQL

07/2017 - 01/2019

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- Published NPM packages, worked on and published Figma and XD plugins, and created a variety of Laravel-based APIs - Designed and implemented several user interface elements in Vue.js, with a focus on the e-book hosting service Stunlab.

EDUCATION

RWANDA CODING ACADEMY